[{"answer": "It's the hardest, most fun work you can imagine.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "How is he feeling on the verge of his big Broadway debut?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "Tonight, they spill his secrets.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Can we get back to talking about me, please?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "Is he a good kisser?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "So-so.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "How good?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "Well, the key about this is that this was when -- forgive me for saying it, but this is when tabloids really mattered.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "How did you find playing a tabloid journalist?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Studying it.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What does it take, do you think, to be a great actor?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "The ones that I admire greatly were Jason Robards and Robert Duvall.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Who are the -- who are greatest actors of your lifetime?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "She was unfortunately very nice about you.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I think finding the right person.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Is there a secret, though?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Do you -- I mean, do you turn it on for your wife, performance-wise?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Now those -- those are for the pilot.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "You mean right now?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "But you know what, we were told, I'm sure you'll recall, the drag element, that's just going to be for the pilot.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Can we just -- can you just put on this wrap?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "He can't hit.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "What is the worst thing you can tell me about Tom Hanks?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "A demanding diva.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Do we?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Well, one cop turned to the other one at one point and said hey, hey, Bill, you know who we have here?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Not surprised but very -- I have to kind of pull it together because I really do -- I get moved as a friend, not merely as a fellow actor and, you know, we're in early scenes together, suddenly, quickly, there's a lot of courage for any actor, and I don't care who it is, and this guy, he's -- he's tearing --", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Have you been surprised by his performances back on a stage like this?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, I will defer to all of Nora's wisdom here.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Have you contemplated the belly flop in this play?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Dear.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Is it comforting working with four very strong actors?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, I had met her briefly, we rehearsed for about a month and then I have decided I wanted to meet her just to meet her without having it affect what we were working on in the room.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "What was that like for you?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "How do you do that?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "That's sweet.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "ORGAN: Is that what she said?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "No, because I understand -- I understand the desire to be in game.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Did you find that difficult?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "IERNEY: And that's what the story is.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Where's the reward> Where's my badge?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Do you ever do that?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "It hasn't softened my fury.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Have any of the views of all of you changed about tabloid?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "But do you -- as some do, do you resent the attention of paparazzi?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Part of the business.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Or are they part of the business?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Is he a good kisser?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "So-so.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "How good?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Not a clue.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Did you know, Tom?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Well, he's the best.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "What was it about Tom, do you think, that your mother loved so much?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Yes, we are.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Are we going to go through them all now?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "And we shared that because of your scene in \"Fences.\"", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "It was that scene where the -- his older son sits down and asks him, you know, why didn't you like me?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "He said you, sir, are a groove.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "What did he say?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Nobody at all.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Nobody?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "If I had three hours to live, I would not be making a movie, sir.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "If I said to you you've got three hours left to live, not that you have, what's the movie you'd make again?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "I'm just proud to have been -- you know, to have done that reading.", "docId": "130321pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "How important is it to you, personally, to be -- and all of you actually to be making what turned out to be Nora's last work?", "qSentId": 698}]